J. D. Sloan Photographs MS247
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographic prints and negatives, 1978 -- 2013; MS247.001; 7.4 Linear Feet
  - Tufts 2002, MS247.001.006.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Greek Orthodox Patriarch Gift of Big Book and Adele Bacow family, 2002-04-17; MS247.001.006.00005.00018 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020417-A 020417-B
    - Tufts Skuse Chair, 2002-04-30; MS247.001.006.00005.00019 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020430-A to 020430-E
    - Tufts: USDA Roche Vitamins, 2002-04-26; MS247.001.006.00005.00020 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020426-A to 020426-D
    - Sol Gittleman Send off Reception ( Step down from Provost), 2002-06-05; MS247.001.006.00005.00021 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020605-A to 020605-H
    - Tufts Light on the Hill, 2002-10-11; MS247.001.006.00005.00022 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      021011-A to 021011-F
    - 2002 Wide Open ( Amy Welch First), 2002-09-30; MS247.001.006.00005.00023 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020930-B to 020930-I
    - Tufts Jumbo Club Distinguished Service, 2002-09-27; MS247.001.006.00005.00024 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      020927-A to 020927-F
  - Tufts 2002 Volume 2, MS247.001.006.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Rocky Carzo's cage Dedication, 2002-09-29; MS247.001.006.00006.00001 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020929-A to 020929-F
    - Tufts Friends of the Library Anne Sauer Picture Book, 2002-03-06; MS247.001.006.00006.00002 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020306-A to 020306-B
    - Tufts: UCCPS 2nd poster session, 2002-10-28; MS247.001.006.00006.00003 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      021028-A to 021028-F
    - Yankee Dental, 2002-02-01; MS247.001.006.00006.00004 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020201-U to 020201-Z
    - Tufts: Omidyar Scholar and Books, 2002-03-07; MS247.001.006.00006.00005 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020307-A to 020307-E
    - Tufts Dental Becky's Career Day, 2002-03-08; MS247.001.006.00006.00006 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020308-A to 020308-B
    - Tufts Dental OKU Dinner, 2002-05-17; MS247.001.006.00006.00007 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020517-A to 020517-E
    - Tufts Medical 2002 Reunion, 2002-05-10; MS247.001.006.00006.00008 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020510-A to 020510-J
    - Tufts Pre Commencement, 2002-05-18; MS247.001.006.00006.00009 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020518-A to 020518-O
    - HNRC @ Tufts, 2002-05-20; MS247.001.006.00006.00010 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020520: solo
    - Golden Crown Award, 2002-05-23; MS247.001.006.00006.00011 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020523:000996
    - Golden Crown Award, 2002-05-23; MS247.001.006.00006.00012 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Tufts Medical MD/MBA Year End Dinner, 2002-05-14; MS247.001.006.00006.00013 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020514-A to 020514-C
    - Tufts Medical Awards Dinner, 2002-05-15; MS247.001.006.00006.00014 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020515-A to 020515-H
    - Tufts: Dental Dinner, 2002-05-09; MS247.001.006.00006.00015 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020509-A to 020509-E
    - Tufts: 2002 Dental Reunion, 2002-05-04; MS247.001.006.00006.00016 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020504-A to 020504-V
    - Dental Commencement, 2002-05-19; MS247.001.006.00006.00017 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020519-A to 020519-N
    - Charles Tufts Luncheon, 2002-05-16; MS247.001.006.00006.00018 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020516-A to 020516-K
    - Tufts Dental 1st Web tour shoot, 2002-07-30; MS247.001.006.00006.00019 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      020730-A to 020730-F
  - Tufts 2000-2005, MS247.001.006.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - 2005 Vet Comeback 1st Hall of Fame Faculty, 2005-09-10; MS247.001.006.00007.00001 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      732-738 7 rolls
      Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine; Sarah Fish
    - Tufts Pops, 2005-05-19; MS247.001.006.00007.00002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      524-528 5 rolls ( stage views)
      Cummings; Foster
    - Tisch Author Talk Catherine Clinton Harriet Tubman, 2005-10-14; MS247.001.006.00007.00003 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      rolls 641, 642, 643
    - Tufts Dental Toast to Tufts, 2005-09-09; MS247.001.006.00007.00004 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      rolls 555-560
    - Tufts Hirsh Tennis Shoot, 2000-01-24; MS247.001.006.00007.00005 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      one roll
    - Joshua Odette plaque deceased dental students, 2005-02-17; MS247.001.006.00007.00006 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      436, 437
    - Tufts Grad Hooding, 2005-05-21; MS247.001.006.00007.00007 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      6 rolls
    - Presidential Symposium, 2005-02-16; MS247.001.006.00007.00008 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Roll 258
    - Presidential Symposium, 2005-02-16; MS247.001.006.00007.00009 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Tufts Dental Hispanic Dinner (H D A), 2005-05-17; MS247.001.006.00007.00010 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      5 rolls 236-240
    - Tufts: oral Surgery Awards Dinner, 2005-06-21; MS247.001.006.00007.00011 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      rolls 982-986
      School of Dental Medicine; Maria Papageorge; Paula
    - Class of DI 2007 Clinical Advancement Ceremony, 2005-07-26; MS247.001.006.00007.00012 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Tufts Graduate Awards, 2005-04-22; MS247.001.006.00007.00013 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      rolls 526-529
    - Dental Chernobal Children, 2005-01-21; MS247.001.006.00007.00014 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      School of Dental Medicine; Maria
    - Tufts Presidential Awards: Citizenship & Public Service, 2005-04-13; MS247.001.006.00007.00015 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Rolls 58-60
    - Dental Development Students & Faculty, 2005-03-10; MS247.001.006.00007.00016 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Roll 914
    - Dental Development Students & Faculty, 2005-03-10; MS247.001.006.00007.00017 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Tufts Dental 2005 White Coat, 2005-03-18; MS247.001.006.00007.00018 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Rolls 205-216
    - Tufts Medical Reunion, 2005; MS247.001.006.00007.00019 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      5061-5051-5052
  - Tufts 2005-2012, MS247.001.006.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - 2005 Medical Reunion, 2005-05-07; MS247.001.006.00008.00001 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      51-71
    - Dental Reunion, 2005-05-14; MS247.001.006.00008.00002 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      19 rolls 399-417 Kugle w/teeth on screen
    - Jumbo Club Awards, 2005; MS247.001.006.00008.00003 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Megerle Portrait 1819-1823
    - UN Flag A & B, 2005; MS247.001.006.00008.00004 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      2064-2065
    - Sol's Lecture, 2005; MS247.001.006.00008.00005 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      2062-2063
    - Tufts SNDA 2010, 2012-05-05; MS247.001.006.00008.00006 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Donna Norris Election Portraits, 2005-09-28; MS247.001.006.00008.00007 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      Rolls 22-24
  - Tufts 2005, MS247.001.006.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Dental family Welcome day for dog, 2005-08-30; MS247.001.006.00009.00001 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      rolls 855-863
    - 2005 Wide Open Amy's Last, MS247.001.006.00009.00002 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      1671-1682
    - 2005 Yankee Dental Marriot Copley, 2005-01-28; MS247.001.006.00009.00003 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      798-802
    - Walk for the Cure Tufts Dental @ UMASS, 2005-09-18; MS247.001.006.00009.00004 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      0671-0672
    - Tufts Dental Awards Dinner, 2005-05-18; MS247.001.006.00009.00005 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      501-507
    - Practices 5-8, 2005-05-11; MS247.001.006.00009.00006 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      negatives (photographs); contact sheets
    - Dental Commencement 2005, 2005-05-22; MS247.001.006.00009.00007 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      8 rolls
  - Tufts 2006, MS247.001.007.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Delta Dental of Mass Professorship in Public Health, 2006-10-24; MS247.001.007.00001.00001 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      7369-7375
    - 2006 Dental Commencement, 2006-05-21; MS247.001.007.00001.00002 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      10 rolls 2641-2650
    - Marty Sherwin Author Talk Pulitzer, 2006-10-10; MS247.001.007.00001.00003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      7272-7275
    - Parents Weekend Author Talk Frank Ackerman, 2006-10-20; MS247.001.007.00001.00004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      2 rolls
    - Tufts 2006 SNDA Awards Dinner, 2006-05-17; MS247.001.007.00001.00005 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      2558-2561
    - HNRC 4th Research Day, 2006; MS247.001.007.00001.00006 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      9394-9405
    - 2006 Dental Welcome Day, MS247.001.007.00001.00007 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      7896-7901
  - Tufts 2006 Volume 2, MS247.001.007.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - International White Coat Dental, 2006-07-24; MS247.001.007.00002.00001 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      6668-6673
    - Perio Dinner Lombardo's, 2006-07-26; MS247.001.007.00002.00002 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      6798-6803
      School of Dental Medicine; Therese Kohlman
    - Yankee Dental 06, 2006-01-27; MS247.001.007.00002.00003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      7844-7848
    - International Food Night, 2006-03-02; MS247.001.007.00002.00004 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      1 roll
    - 2006 Jumbo Club Awards, 2006-04-01; MS247.001.007.00002.00005 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      8928-8931
    - Tisch Author Talk Tony Massarotti, 2006-02-09; MS247.001.007.00002.00006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      1 roll 7915
    - 2006 H D A Awards Dinner, MS247.001.007.00002.00007 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      9948-9953
    - 2006 Dental Wards Dinner, MS247.001.007.00002.00008 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      9909-9915
    - 1st Marian Balmuth Lecture (Classics), 2006-04-18; MS247.001.007.00002.00009 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      9280-9283
    - 2006 Grad Hooding, MS247.001.007.00002.00010 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      7 rolls 2667-2673
    - 2006 OKU Awards Dinner Tufts Dental, MS247.001.007.00002.00011 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      5 rolls 2606-2610
    - 2006 White Coat Dental Advancement, MS247.001.007.00002.00012 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      8714-8727 14 rolls
      School of Dental Medicine; Jamshed Bharucha
    - Oral Surgery Dinner 2006, 2006-06-21; MS247.001.007.00002.00013 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      9359-9362 4 rolls
      School of Dental Medicine; Maria Papageorge
- Born digital materials, circa 1995 -- 2013; MS247.002; 1 Linear Feet
  This series is open for research, but is minimally processed and may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  This series contains 294 CDs of digital photographs taken by J. D. Sloan, documenting university events and campus life.
  - Binder A, 1995 -- 2010; MS247.001378 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts Tomorrow Neubauer, 1995 November 4; MS247.001379; Gittleman, Sol, 1934- (Box 7, Folder 3)
      951104 CD
      Medford Campus
      Civil War
    - Tufts Dental 04 Bates/ Andrews poster session, 2004 March 3; MS247.001380 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040303 A-F
      Boston Campus; School of Dental Medicine
    - Tufts: UCCPS Film Fest Slavery, 2003 December 3; MS247.001381 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      030203 A-B
    - Tufts Foster Small Animal Hospital Dedication, 2003 November 1; MS247.001382 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      031101 CD
      Agnes Varis
    - Tufts Presidential Symposium, 2004 February 18; MS247.001383 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040218 A-E
    - Tufts UCCPS Poster Session, 2004 March 3; MS247.001384 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040303 V-Z
    - Shapiro Awards, 2004 March 30; MS247.001385 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040330 A and B
    - Tufts Brian O'Connell, 2004 May 13; MS247.001386 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040513 263-265
    - 100 Anniversary of John A Holmes, 2004 April 23; MS247.001387 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040423 A-D
    - Tufts Presidents Awards Brian O'Connell, 2004 April 14; MS247.001388 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040404 4 rolls
    - Tufts Videos UCCPS Screening, 2004 April 26; MS247.001389 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040426 A345-C347
    - UCCPS / President's Awards, 2004; MS247.001390 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Medical Reunion, 2004 May 07; MS247.001391 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040507 CD
      Boston Campus; School of Medicine
    - Dr. Briss Tiff Portraits, 2004 May 18; MS247.001392 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040518 483 and 484
    - Tufts/ Tisch Berger Demonstrations, 2004 April 29; MS247.001393 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040429 450-452
    - Pops, 2004 May 20; MS247.001394 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040520 981-984
    - Commencement Robing and Stage, 2004 May 23; MS247.001395 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040523 739-743
      Judy Olson; Medford Campus
    - Charles Tufts Luncheon, 2004 May 20; MS247.001396 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040520 568-569
    - Charles Tufts Luncheon, 2004 May 20; MS247.001397 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      2nd disc
    - Tisch Robert Preston, 1996 October 9; MS247.001398 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      961009 CD
    - SNDA Dinner (Margaret Howard Portrait), 2004; MS247.001399 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls: 485-489
    - Tufts Graduate School Hooding, 2004 May 22; MS247.001400 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040522:955-958
    - Tufts Ortho Dept Picture, 2004 June 1; MS247.001401 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040601 solo (7152)
      Dr Briss; Dr Gheewalla
    - Tufts Graduate Hooding, 2004 May 22; MS247.001402 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040522G 955-958
    - Tufts Commencement Related, 2004 May 22; MS247.001403 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040522:833and834
    - Tufts University College Service Day at Cummings Scl., 2004 May 22; MS247.001404 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040522-Rolls 835-840
    - Dean Eileen Kennedy Friedman Nutrition, 2004 August 17; MS247.001405 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040817 714-718
      Boston Campus; Friedman School of Nutrition Science and Policy
    - The First Day for Tufts Dental, 2004 August 31; MS247.001406 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040831 CD
    - Vendors in the Dining Hall Locally grown apples, 2004 October 21; MS247.001407 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      041021:117-121
      Julie Lampie; Medford Campus
    - University College Mock Presidential Debate in Cabot, 2004 October 26; MS247.001408 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      041026 3453
      Roberta Ostersachs
    - Tufts Parents Weekend, 2004 October 23; MS247.001409 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      041023 rolls 137-152
    - Parents Weekend Author Talks RA Salvatore, 2004 October 23; MS247.001410 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      041023:061
    - UN Flag Raising Parents Weekend, 2004 October 24; MS247.001411 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      041024 CD
    - Sol Gittleman St. Hillel Lecture Parents Weekend, 2004 October 24; MS247.001412 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      041024 rolls 062 and 063
    - Vet reunion 04, 2004 August 7; MS247.001413 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040807 rolls 156 -162
    - International Student White Coat Ceremony, 2004 September 7; MS247.001414 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040907:299-302
    - Sol Gittleman's Author Talk, 2004 December 1; MS247.001415 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      041201 rolls 900and901
    - Tufts Dranetz Tower Tisch Library, 2004 September 8; MS247.001416 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      040908:055-58
    - Tufts Faculty Advancement Ceremony Tisch, 2004 November 18; MS247.001417 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      041118 398-400
    - Tufts Pat Campbell's Goodbye, 2004 December 8; MS247.001418 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      467-471
    - Kroll Family Statue Unveiling Tisch Library, 2004 December 5; MS247.001419 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      9 rolls
    - 2nd John Holmes Poetry Reading Coolidge Rm, 2005 April 5; MS247.001420 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Richard Wilbur; Medford Campus
    - Tufts Vet Reunion in Providence, 2004 August 4; MS247.001421 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      1st 20 yr reunion class
    - Dranetz Café: Tufts/Tisch Library, 2005; MS247.001422 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts: Author Talk Lynne Cox Swimming to Antarctica, 2005 February 2; MS247.001423 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Bacow's Presidential Symposium Coolidge Room, 2005 February 16; MS247.001424 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Maria's Dental Development Shoot, 2005 March 10; MS247.001425 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Dental White Coat Clinical Advancement ceremony, 2005 March 18; MS247.001426 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Hyatt Regency
    - 25th Football Anniversary Celebration of Tufts, 2004 October 23; MS247.001427 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      undefeated football season
    - Tufts Author Talk Christopher Castellami, 2005 March 29; MS247.001428 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      A Kiss from Maddelena
    - Tufts 25th Anniversary Undefeated football team, 2004 October 23; MS247.001429 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Matt Penney's Jumbo Club Awards, 2005; MS247.001430 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      swim team holding Coach Don Megerle's portrait
    - Tufts Graduate Awards, 2005; MS247.001431 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      made 2 discs
      Charlene Carle; Medford Campus
    - Tufts presidential awards for citizenship and public service, 2005 April 13; MS247.001432 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      58,59,60
    - Tufts Film Festival University College, 2005 May 2; MS247.001433 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 869-874
      Margaret Lazarus
    - Hispanic HAD Dinner, 2005 May 11; MS247.001434 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      236-240
    - Student National Dental Association Dinner, 2005; MS247.001435 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Dental Reunion, 2005 May 14; MS247.001436 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 399-417
    - Tufts Medical Reunion, 2005 May 07; MS247.001437 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 2nd disc Tufts Medical Reunion, 2005 May 07; MS247.001438 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts Night at the Pops, 2005 May 19; MS247.001439 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 524-528
    - Bates/Andrew Dinner at Caprice Restaurant, 2005 May 17; MS247.001440 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      3 rolls
      Dean Rosenblatt; School of Medicine
    - Dental Awards Dinner, 2005 May 18; MS247.001441 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 501-507 7 rolls
    - Dental Commencement, 2005 May 22; MS247.001442 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 698-705 8 rolls
    - Grad Hooding, 2005 May 21; MS247.001443 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 714-719
    - Dental O.K.U Awards Dinner, 2005 May 20; MS247.001444 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      4 rolls 691,693,694,695
    - Oral Surgery Awards Dinner, 2005 June 21; MS247.001445 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      982-986 5 rolls
      Dr. Maria Papageorge
    - IRT Classes and Group Alex's last year Ritter did College 4, 2005 July 19; MS247.001446 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      4 rolls 46-49
    - Class of 2007's Joshua O'Dette plaque, 2005 February 17; MS247.001447 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Dental students who died before graduation 436-437
    - International Student Advancement Ceremony white coat, 2005 July 26; MS247.001448 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      662-665
    - Dental Faculty Recognition Luncheon, 2005 August 5; MS247.001449 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      788-794 Boston Harbor Hotel
    - Perio Grad Party at Lombardo's, 2005 July 27; MS247.001450 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      796-801 8 rolls
    - Vet Comeback 1st as Cummings School, 2005 September 10; MS247.001451 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      332-338 7 rolls
      Grafton Campus; Cummings School of Veterinary Medicine
    - 2005 Dental Family Welcome Day Main disc, 2005 August 30; MS247.001452 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 855-860
    - 2005 Dental Family Welcome Day 2nd disc Family Life Panel, 2005 August 30; MS247.001453 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 861-863
    - Tufts First Ever Research Day, 2005 October 31; MS247.001454 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      rolls 38-43 Infectious Diseases and Pathogens
    - Sackler 25th Anniversary, 2005 October 21; MS247.001455 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      12 rolls
      Peggy Newell; Carie Thomas; Boston Campus; Sackler School of Graduate Biomedical Sciences
    - Tufts Athletics Distinguished Service Awards, 2005 October 14; MS247.001456 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Nancy Stern: ABC twin NBC
    - Tisch Author Talk famous parents weekend, 2005 October 14; MS247.001457 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Harriett Tubman Catherine Clinton rolls 641-643
    - Author Talk Nina Silber, 2005 November 3; MS247.001458 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Northern Women 166-167
    - Dental Donor Dinner 2nd Annual Toast to Tufts, 2005 September 5; MS247.001459 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Colonade Hotel 555-560 6 rolls
    - 2nd Research Day obesity etc., 2005; MS247.001460 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      opens hard rolls 1 screwed up 2-9
    - 2nd Research Day obesity etc., 2005; MS247.001461 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      opens well rolls 10-13
    - Bates Day Tufts Dental, 2006 February 22; MS247.001462 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Disc 1 of 2
      Ilene Doherty; School of Dental Medicine
    - Bates Day Tufts Dental, 2006 February 22; MS247.001463 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Disc 2 of 2
      Ilene Doherty
    - Tufts Tisch Library Talks Tony Masserati, 2006 February 9; MS247.001464 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Julie Lampie Food International Night, 2006 March 2; MS247.001465 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 2003 Parents Weekend, 2003 October 25; MS247.001466 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Ellie Short's last production
    - Tufts 2010 Balmuth, 2010 February 8; MS247.001467 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Morphology of objects (cologne )
      Reinhard Foertsch
    - Tufts 2010 Bates Day, MS247.001468 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Bates Day 189 items
    - 2010 Bates Day presentations, MS247.001469 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Bates Day Presentations
    - Tufts First Half White Coat Presentation, 2010; MS247.001470 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      A43-204 152 Frames
    - Tufts Second Half White Coat Presentation, 2010; MS247.001471 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      B205-407 169 frames
    - Tufts First Half White Coat Presentation, 2010; MS247.001472 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts Second Half White Coat Presentation, 2010; MS247.001473 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts 2010 Frank Ackerman Tisch Author Talks, 2010 February 25; MS247.001474 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      best edit "Can we afford the future"
    - Tufts 2010 Frank Ackerman Tisch Author Talks, 2010 February 25; MS247.001475 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      case exhibit for Barbara Grossman
    - 2010 John Holmes Poetry Tisch Author Talk, 2010 April 9; MS247.001476 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      David Ferry
    - 2010 Graduate School Student Awards, 2010 April 23; MS247.001477 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      144 frames
    - Tufts 2010 TUD Grads Commencement, MS247.001478 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts 2010 Senior Awards Dinner Tufts Dental, 2010 May 7; MS247.001479 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts H D A 2010 Awards Dinner Tufts Dental, MS247.001480 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts SNDA 2010, MS247.001481 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts 2010 Dental Eight Student Practices, MS247.001482 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - 2010 Bates Andrews Awards Dinner, 2010 May 19; MS247.001483 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts 2010 SNDA Awards Dinner, 2010 May 17; MS247.001484 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      militant speaker Dr Walter Owens
    - 2010 Tufts Student Dental Practices 8 groups, MS247.001485 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts Dr. LaCourse, 2010 May 23; MS247.001486 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Captain, best regards
    - 2010 Graduate Hooding, MS247.001487 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Ballou Medford
    - Tufts Dental Commencement disc B, 2010 May 23; MS247.001488 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Medford Campus; School of Dental Medicine
    - Tufts Dental Commencement disc A, 2010 May 23; MS247.001489 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Connie Putnam's Plaque on the Track, 2010 May 22; MS247.001490 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Steeple Chase Courts
    - Tufts Tisch Berger Demos, 2010 May 3; MS247.001491 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Blank CD, circa 2010; MS247.001492 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Surgery Dinner Tufts Dental 2010, 2010 June 29; MS247.001493 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Dental White Coat Ceremony, 2010 July 14; MS247.001494 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts Dental Recognition Lunch, 2010 August 6; MS247.001495 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      A 5065-5186
    - Tufts Dental Recognition Lunch, 2010 August 6; MS247.001496 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      B 5187-5317
    - International Dental Students White Coat, 2010 July 14; MS247.001497 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Clinical Advancement Ceremony
    - Author Talk David Carroll Turtles, 2010 October 22; MS247.001498 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Tufts Dining Jumbo Shoot, 2010 October 22; MS247.001499 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      Lyza Bayard
  - Binder B, 2000 -- 2010; MS247.001500 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Tisch Library Dedication Scans, 1996 October 9; MS247.001501 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Matt Penney's Jumbo Club Awards, 2006 April 2; MS247.001502 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      2006 Jumbo Club Awards
      Matt Penney
    - Tufts 2006 Entrepreneurship Competitions, 2006 April 6; MS247.001503 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      Business plan and Frignon social
      Pam Goldberg
    - Tufts HDA Dinner, 2006 May 15; MS247.001504 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      HDA Dinner Dental